<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
<channel>

<title>Trinity Church of Nashville</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org</link>
<description>Sermons at Trinity Church by Dr. Matt McCullough and others.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2010 12:00:00 CDT</lastBuildDate>
<itunes:author>Matt McCullough</itunes:author>
<itunes:keywords>reformed, gospel, baptist, eakin, grace, dave hunt</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:image href="http://tcnash.org/img/podcast4.png" />
<image>
  <url>http://tcnash.org/img/podcast4.png</url>
  <title>Trinity Church of Nashville</title>
  <link>http://tcnash.org</link>
  <width>480</width>
  <height>480</height>
</image>
<itunes:owner>
  <itunes:email>tech@tcnash.org</itunes:email>
  <itunes:name>Drew Raines</itunes:name>
</itunes:owner>
<category>Religion &amp; Spirituality</category>
<category>Christianity</category>
<itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">
  <itunes:category text="Christianity" />
</itunes:category>
<copyright>&#xA9;2010 Trinity Church of Nashville. This work is licensed
under a Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial-No Derivative Works
3.0 United States License. To view a copy of this license, visit
http://creativecommons.org/licensenc-nd/3.0/us/</copyright>

<item>
<title>In the Beginning - Genesis 1:1-27</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  The story of Genesis--a book
of beginnings--opens with a poem that answers questions as old as
time: Where did we come from?  Why is there something rather than
nothing?  And who is in charge?</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 12:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
<guid>BCC0C78F-BB7E-42C3-BC7F-61661BC7A60B</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-04-03-Gen-1-In-The-Beginning.mp3" length="16219910" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:44:53</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jesus Is Alive - Mark 15:40-16:8</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  Mark concludes his story with
an earth-shattering claim that launches the life of the church: Jesus
was really dead, but now he's alive.  He leaves us to ask two
questions.  Is it true?  And if it is true, if Jesus really is alive,
what are the implications?</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 12:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
<guid>288EEE76-FF31-4066-A83C-07FC98D5F382</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-03-20-Mark-16-Jesus-Is-Alive.mp3" length="15138348" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:41:53</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Why Did Jesus Die? - Mark 14:53-65, 15:1-39</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  Mark's Gospel has been
building to the death of Jesus all along, but it's also raised a
crucial question: why must Jesus die?  Mark's telling of Jesus's trial
and crucifixion removes a couple possible explanations.  Jesus didn't
die because he was guilty: the trial of Jesus shows no one found any
legitimate legal reason to kill him.  And Jesus didn't die because he
was powerless: Mark's readers know Jesus is innocent and has power to
overcome his captors, but he doesn't defend himself.  So why then?
Jesus died to establish a kingdom you could live in.  Mark's chief
irony and his central message is that Jesus comes to power and invites
us into his kingdom through his death.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 12:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
<guid>C89372E3-7E9C-4BE8-809C-9DB182585BBE</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-03-13-Mark-15-Why-Did-Jesus-Die.mp3" length="16077035" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:44:29</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jesus, Our Substitute - Mark 14:1-52</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  Describing the events leading
to Jesus's arrest and crucifixion, Mark tells us a great deal about
what Jesus came here to do: He came to be abandoned so we won't have
to be.  Jesus was abandoned by everyone--Judas, Peter, his disciples,
even his Father--and, remarkably, he chose to have it that way.  Why
did he choose this path of excruciating isolation?  Because through
his death--the ultimate abandonment--he established a covenant
relationship that will never break.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>FDAB186D-E55D-4AFE-8669-9E8AA9B8FF52</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-03-06-Mark-14-Jesus-Our-Substitute.mp3" length="13904538" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:38:27</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jesus on the Future - Mark 13</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  In the longest section of
teaching recorded in Mark's Gospel, Jesus turns to questions asked by
the religious and the philosophical since the beginning of time.  What
does the future hold, and how should we live now in light of that
future?  The details of Jesus's predictions--about the destruction of
the Temple in the near future and about his final return in power and
glory--have always baffled interpreters.  But the bottom line couldn't
be more clear: because Jesus is coming back in victory and judgment,
and because we don't know when, our responsibility is to trust Jesus
and stay ready.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>9730C3A9-3231-43F7-A822-16E9BB1549FB</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-02-27-Mark-13-The-Future.mp3" length="13572564" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:37:32</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Religious Hypocrisy and the Love of God - Mark 11:27-12:44</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  After a parable of judgment
that sets the stage for his confrontation with Israel's religious
leaders, Jesus fields challenges from each primary group of leaders:
the Pharisees, the Sadducees, and the scribes.  In each case, Jesus's
answers turn the tables on his challengers to expose their hypocrisy.
In the end, Jesus proposes the only solution to religious hypocrisy: a
love of God for God's sake and with everything you have.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>B7E712D6-238E-4F4B-A6FD-30FECC8292FB</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-02-20-Mark-12-Religious-Hypocrisy.mp3" length="17058666" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:47:13</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>The King Has Come - Mark 11:1-25</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  Chapter 11 marks Jesus's
arrival at Jersalem, an event laced through with prophecy fulfillment.
Here, by an "enacted parable" and by a dramatic confrontation in the
Temple, Jesus shows more of what he's come to do.  As King, he's come
to purge and to restore.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>37DB54F8-5F65-4789-AC6E-0296CF8DFE87</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-02-13-Mark-11-King-Has-Come.mp3" length="14688988" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:40:38</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Kingdom Citizenship - Mark 10:13-52</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  To this point Mark's narrative
has promised that Jesus would, paradoxically, establish the kingdom of
God through his death.  So what does this mean for who belongs to the
kingdom and how?  Mark answers this question by contrasting stories on
faith with stories on self-reliance.  In short, the kingdom belongs to
the desperate, not the self-reliant, because it belongs to those who
rest only on Jesus.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>0D4088D9-DD6C-4B79-AEEC-8A54A3EF3FED</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-02-06-Mark-10-Kingdom-Citizenship.mp3" length="16586268" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:45:54</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Marriage by Design, Marriage in Reality - Mark 10:1-12</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  Still on the road towards
Jerusalem, Jesus shifts the focus of his teaching on discipleship to
the subject of marriage and divorce.  As so often before, he explodes
standard religious convention.  Jesus answers a question from the
Pharisees about divorce with an explanation of God's original design
for marriage.  Marriage viewed from the perspective of creation, in
the eyes of God, is an unbreakable bond.  But how do we square Jesus?s
marriage ideal with our experience in a world deeply marred by
sin?</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>52E931A2-2493-4692-89B0-8483AE7F0CF0</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-01-30-Mark-10-Marriage-Design-Reality.mp3" length="13635428" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:37:42</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Living the Cross-Centered Life - Mark 9:30-50</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  As Jesus makes his way towards
Jerusalem and the death that's waiting there for him, he narrows his
focus to teaching his disciples what it means to follow a Messiah who
suffers.  The cross sets the pattern for Christian discipleship, and
this text offers concrete examples.  A life modeled on the cross is a
life that puts the interests of others above its own, and it's a life
that fights a radical battle with sin.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>C8A2D3F1-C8F0-449E-B605-60CB58FA8A61</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-01-23-Mark-9-Cross-Centered-Life.mp3" length="17345803" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:48:01</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Belief, Unbelief, and the Saving Power of Jesus - Mark 9:14-29</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  In this story of demon possession and exorcism, Mark returns to one of his favorite questions: what must we do to claim the saving power of Jesus?  It's a story that illustrates what we know from our own experience: unbelief comes from many sources and in many forms.  But in the desperate plea of a helpless father Mark illustrates another, even more powerful truth.  It's a decision to rest on Jesus--not mathematical certainty--which constitutes the faith that leads to deliverance.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>69A35009-EAD3-4E09-8248-3472C38BAF53</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-01-16-Mark-9-Belief-Unbelief-Power.mp3" length="16250543" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:44:58</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Glory, Shame, and the Christian Paradox - Mark 9:1-13</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  Just after Jesus has told his disciples that he must suffer and die, and that following him means they will suffer too, Jesus reinforces their confidence in him with a glimpse of his glory, a mysterious event called the transfiguration.  In this story and in Jesus's discussion with his disciples about this event, Mark helps us understand a central Christian paradox: as Son of God Jesus is undeniably glorious, but his glory as Messiah comes through a death of unimaginable shame.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>F39CE5DA-06C2-4087-A793-C99E4B24A207</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-01-09-Mark-9-Glory-Shame-Paradox.mp3" length="14185091" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:39:14</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jesus Is the Christ - A Review of Mark 1-8</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  The stories of Jesus's life
and teaching in Mark's Gospel are designed to answer three main
questions: who is Jesus, what did Jesus come here to do, and what does
that require of us?  Already, in chapters 1-8, we've seen the shape of
Mark's answer to those crucial questions emerge.  First, Jesus is the
divine Son of God, as shown in his unmatched words and actions of
authority and power.  Second, he came to fix what was broken, to
establish the kingdom of God by his life, death, and resurrection.
And, finally, Jesus demands absolute submission from us: a repentance
from all competing allegiances, a rest in the sufficiency of his power
and love, and a willigness to follow him with a life of
self-denial.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>DC3691E3-F47C-42D3-A472-EF5FD9AA9DE9</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2011-01-02-A-Review-Of-Mark-1-8.mp3" length="19125416" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:45:23</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Christmas and the Story of Salvation - Isaiah 9:1-7</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  To fully appreciate why
Jesus's birth matters so much, we have to understand where it falls in
the overarching story the Bible tells about God's work of salvation.
Isaiah 9 offers one of the most important clues, hundreds of years
before Jesus was actually born. The prophet claims that the people who
walked in darkness have seen a light because a child was born.  In
other words, we've got to understand the meaning of this darkness and
we've got to understand the meaning of this light if we're to
understand the meaning of the child.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2010 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>3546B7B2-5850-4912-A014-3ABEBB76B41D</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-12-19-Christmas-Story-of-Salvation.mp3" length="16454242" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:39:02</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Christ, the Cross, and Christian Discipleship - Mark 8:31-38</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  This exchange between Jesus
and his disciples represents a turning point in Mark's Gospel.  Just
after Peter's climactic confession of Jesus as the Christ, Jesus
explains what kind of Christ he would be and what that implied for all
who would follow him.  Jesus explains to his followers--and to
us--that there is no Christ without the cross and resurrection, and
there is no Christian discipleship without suffering.
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>D5907381-7B19-43F6-9631-E96F4C6D2105</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-12-12-Mark-8-Christ-Cross-Discipleship.mp3" length="17235963" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<itunes:duration>00:40:53</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Seeing and Believing - Mark 8:1-30</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>
Speaker: Matt McCullough.  In this cluster of stories Mark helps
explain why people respond to Jesus in very different ways, some in
faith and others with persistent unbelief. Contrasting the disciples'
struggle to believe even after all they'd seen with Peter's dramatic
confession of Jesus as the Christ, Mark shows us that spiritual sight
is never the same thing as physical sight. Faith--seeing with new
eyes--is a gift of God.
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2010 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>6D0267A2-7513-4550-A57A-EE9B90979655</guid>
<enclosure url='http://media.tcnash.org/2010-12-05-Mark-8-Seeing-and-Believing.mp3' length='17001535' type='audio/mpeg'/>
<itunes:duration>00:40:20</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jesus's Radical Message of Sin and Salvation - Mark 7</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough. In chapter 7, by relating
Jesus's confrontation with the Pharisees along with his ministry among
the Gentiles, Mark exposes the two sides of Jesus's radical message:
the problem of sin is universal, but the promise of salvation is
universal too.
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>27E64F6E-3B97-4617-ACA6-1E3FFE3A7E8C-2</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-11-28-Mark-7-Jesus-Radical-Message.mp3" length="18646509" type="audio/mpeg" />
<itunes:duration>00:44:15</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Rooted in God's Word - Psalm 119</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: John Kramp. In this psalm, a memoir of life
lived through God's word, we are challenged to cultivate both depth
and breadth in our understanding of scripture and to apply God's Word
to the raw circumstances of real life.
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>702F20E5-0A7B-4417-89FF-068741BFAF1E-2</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-11-21-Psalm-119-Rooted-In-Gods-Word.mp3" length="15088478" type="audio/mpeg" />
<itunes:duration>00:35:47</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Overexposure and Underappreciation - Mark 6:1-56</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough. In chapter 6 Mark illustrates
how we should respond to Jesus by contrast to two more examples of
unbelief.  People in Jesus's hometown were offended by his claims to
authority because they'd been inoculated through overexposure.  They
were familiar with Jesus as brother and son and carpenter, but he
seemed too familiar for them to accept his radical words or actions.
Jesus's disciples struggle with another sort of unbelief, which Mark
illustrates with the stories of Jesus feeding 5000 people and Jesus
walking on water.  Confronted with vivid danger, the disciples respond
in fear because, as Mark explains, they failed to appreciate the
significance of Jesus's miraculous provision in the past.
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>2D2AC9CD-391C-418A-96DD-04260C581AC0</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-11-14-Mark-6-Overexposure-Underappreciation.mp3" length="16279339" type="audio/mpeg" />
<itunes:duration>00:38:42</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jesus Is More Powerful - Mark 4:35-5:43</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough. Mark demonstrates in these
stories that Jesus is more powerful than nature, evil, sickness, and
even death.  In each case, the person or group afflicted with their
malady is paralized by fear.  Jesus's response to them is his message
to us, "Do not fear, only believe."
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 12:00:00 CST</pubDate>
<guid>A7B40359-F67D-493F-9EBC-80A237399F58</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-11-07-Mark-4-Jesus-Is-More-Powerful.mp3" length="20158750" type="audio/mpeg" />
<itunes:duration>00:47:51</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Kingdom Is Like... - Mark 4:21-34</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  In this batch of parables
Jesus explains what the kingdom is like by analogy to familiar images,
all of which aim to show why the kingdom doesn't look like most
expected. The kingdom is like a lamp which, though hidden initially,
is ultimately brought in to be revealed. It's like a seed that grows
even though the farmer merely goes to sleep and wakes up again; in
other words, kingdom growth is inevitable because God alone makes it
grow. And the kingdom is like a mustard seed, small in its beginning
but unmatched in its end. If this is what the kingdom is like, how do
we respond?
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 12:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
<guid>9CE50141-A1C7-4E2E-83FA-B9ECE799F7A3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-10-31-Mark-4-The-Kingdom-Is-Like.mp3" length="17464315" type="audio/mpeg" />
<itunes:duration>00:41:26</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>What Do We Do With Jesus? - Mark 3:7-35</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  There is more than one way to
respond to the claims and work of Jesus.  Mark gives us three options.
We can respond by calling him a crazy eccentric, an evil demon, or
Lord.
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
<guid>B18C2ACB-466E-4B92-BB3D-A610A86D8B12</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-10-17-Mark-3-What-Do-We-Do-With-Jesus.mp3" length="17156706" type="audio/mpeg" />
<itunes:duration>00:40:42</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jesus and Religion-as-Usual - Mark 2:18-3:6</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough. Mark begins to document the
opposition that builds against Jesus, ultimately leading to his
execution.  Why did the religious leaders, who were experts of the
law, fail to understand the signficance of Jesus and his kingdom?  How
do we avoid similar error? (We apologize that this recording is
missing the first two minutes. -Ed)
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 12:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
<guid>BBDE8880-4CAB-4014-95F7-E1F9A54C9F77-3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-10-10-Mark-2-3-Jesus-And-Religion.mp3" length="15412664" type="audio/mpeg" />
<itunes:duration>00:36:33</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Will You Be Forgiven? - Mark 2:1-17</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough. At the beginning of chapter 2,
Mark reveals new dimensions of Jesus's identity and mission.  Mark's
stories show that Jesus has the unique ability to forgive sins, and
that this is precisely what he came here to do.  The only question,
then, is whether you will come to Jesus for forgiveness.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 12:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
<guid>C9937A9F-CD70-4526-AD64-B8FA3BEBB914</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-10-03-Mark-2-Will-You-Be-Forgiven.mp3" length="15765414" type="audio/mpeg" />
<itunes:duration>00:37:23</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jesus's Liberating Authority - Mark 1:16-45</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough. In this passage Mark tells a group of stories designed to show that Jesus came preaching the kingdom with a remarkably distinctive authority.  But these stories also reveal a paradoxical truth: submission to Jesus's loving authority sets you free.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2010 10:30:00 CDT</pubDate>
<guid>4AC18ACB-3F05-4F2A-9B22-26FEC7D498F9-3</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-09-26-Mark-1-Jesus-Liberating-Authority.mp3" length="16064383" type="audio/mpeg" />
<itunes:duration>00:38:06</itunes:duration>
</item>

<item>
<title>Who Is Jesus? - Mark 1:1-16</title>
<link>http://tcnash.org/audio.html</link>
<description>Speaker: Matt McCullough.  In order to consider the gospel of Jesus Christ about which Mark writes, we must ask answer three questions: Who is Jesus?  What did he come here to do?  What does he require of us?</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2010 10:30:00 CDT</pubDate>
<guid>08D5A32B-6C18-4F13-AE4C-76478E54A218</guid>
<enclosure url="http://media.tcnash.org/2010-09-19-Mark-1-Who-Is-Jesus.mp3" length="20914835" type="audio/mpeg" />
<itunes:duration>00:43:34</itunes:duration>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
